<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Natan Maia Morette</title>
    <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Natan Maia Morette</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nmmorette.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser Secure Command - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-secure-command-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-secure-command-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>Secure Command Introduction Secure Shell (SSH) is a protocol used to securely access and manage devices on a network. It encrypts data to protect confidentiality and integrity, making SSH a preferred option over Telnet for remote administration.
What is SSH? SSH is a cryptographic network protocol that facilitates secure communication over an unsecured network. Originally designed as a replacement for insecure protocols like Telnet, SSH ensures confidentiality and integrity of data exchanged between two networked devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser 007 - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-007-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-007-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>007 Introduction Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) has become an indispensable tool in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape, enabling seamless remote access to computers and servers from anywhere in the world.
What is Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP)? Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) is a proprietary protocol developed by Microsoft, designed to facilitate remote desktop connections between computers over a network connection. It allows users to access and control a remote computer as if they were physically present at the machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser Reddict - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-reddict-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-reddict-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>Reddict Introduction Redis, short for Remote Dictionary Server, has emerged as a cornerstone in modern software development, revolutionizing how data is stored, cached, and processed. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into the depths of Redis, exploring its features, use cases, and best practices. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned developer seeking to optimize performance or a newcomer intrigued by the buzz surrounding Redis, this blog post aims to provide you with a thorough understanding of its capabilities and potential applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser Arrow - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-arrow-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-arrow-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>Arrow Introduction Telnet, short for Telecommunication Network, is a protocol used for remote terminal connections, allowing users to interact with a computer or network device over a network. Despite its age and simplicity, Telnet still plays a role in various networking scenarios. However, its lack of security features makes it a risky choice in today&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity landscape.
What is Telnet? Telnet operates on the Application Layer of the OSI model and uses a client-server architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser File Hunter - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-file-hunter-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-file-hunter-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>File Hunter Introduction File Transfer Protocol (FTP) is a standard network protocol used for transferring files between a client and a server on a computer network. Since its inception in the early days of the internet, FTP has remained a popular choice for facilitating file transfers, despite the emergence of more secure alternatives. In this blog post, we will delve into the fundamentals of FTP, its operation, security considerations, and alternatives available in today&amp;rsquo;s technology landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review eJPTv2 - Junior Penetration Tester</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/review-ejptv2-junior-penetration-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/review-ejptv2-junior-penetration-tester/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is my review of the eJPTv2 certification offered by INE. Initially, I purchased the voucher for the exam, version V1, without including the training. Later, I was able to exchange it for the V2 version with INE, a process that went smoothly and without complications or costs.
I decided not to participate in the training offered by INE, a choice based on my pre-existing experience in the field. This experience led me to believe that I already had the necessary knowledge to take the eJPT exam without the need for additional preparation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>eJPTv2 - Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/ejptv2-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/ejptv2-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer  This is merely a suggestion based on the tools I personally found useful during the test. I encourage you to take your own notes and tailor your preparation to best suit your needs for the exam
 For additional details about the Exam, please refer to my exam Review post: eJPT Review
Recommended Tools  Nmap Dirbuster nikto WPSCan CrackMapExec The Metasploit Framework SearchSploit Hydra  1. Assessment Methodologies  Ping Sweep fping -a -g 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Nmap Cheat Sheet for Quick Reference</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/the-essential-nmap-cheat-sheet-for-quick-reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/the-essential-nmap-cheat-sheet-for-quick-reference/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Nmap (Network Mapper) is an open-source tool for network exploration and security auditing. Widely used by network administrators, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for vulnerability scanning and network inventory. This cheat sheet provides a quick reference to the most commonly used Nmap commands and options, ideal for both beginners and experienced users.
Basic Scanning Techniques  Basic Network Scan: Command: nmap [target]  Use to quickly scan a target IP or domain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review CNSP - Certified Network Security Practitioner</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/11/review-cnsp-certified-network-security-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/11/review-cnsp-certified-network-security-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>CNSP - Certified Network Security Practitioner Who Should Take This Exam? CNSP (Certified Network Security Professional) is a certification designed for a wide range of professionals in the cybersecurity field. It&amp;rsquo;s particularly suitable for security engineers, network architects, penetration testers, and members of red and blue teams. Moreover, it&amp;rsquo;s an excellent choice for any security enthusiast who aims to test and enhance their understanding of network security.
In my view, professionals with experience in networking or cybersecurity will find the exam relatively easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TryHackme - Rootme - Write-Up</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/11/tryhackme-rootme-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/11/tryhackme-rootme-write-up/</guid>
      <description>RootMe A ctf for beginners, can you root me?
https://tryhackme.com/room/rrootme
Enumeration nmap Initial enumeration with nmap
nmap 10.10.88.1 Starting Nmap 7.94SVN ( https://nmap.org ) at 2023-11-21 05:03 PST Nmap scan report for 10.10.88.1 Host is up (0.32s latency). Not shown: 996 closed tcp ports (conn-refused) PORT STATE SERVICE 1/tcp filtered tcpmux 22/tcp open ssh 80/tcp open http 2200/tcp filtered ici Nmap done: 1 IP address (1 host up) scanned in 27.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
