<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>review on Natan Maia Morette</title>
    <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in review on Natan Maia Morette</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nmmorette.github.io/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review eJPTv2 - Junior Penetration Tester</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/review-ejptv2-junior-penetration-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/review-ejptv2-junior-penetration-tester/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is my review of the eJPTv2 certification offered by INE. Initially, I purchased the voucher for the exam, version V1, without including the training. Later, I was able to exchange it for the V2 version with INE, a process that went smoothly and without complications or costs.
I decided not to participate in the training offered by INE, a choice based on my pre-existing experience in the field. This experience led me to believe that I already had the necessary knowledge to take the eJPT exam without the need for additional preparation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review CNSP - Certified Network Security Practitioner</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/11/review-cnsp-certified-network-security-practitioner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/11/review-cnsp-certified-network-security-practitioner/</guid>
      <description>CNSP - Certified Network Security Practitioner Who Should Take This Exam? CNSP (Certified Network Security Professional) is a certification designed for a wide range of professionals in the cybersecurity field. It&amp;rsquo;s particularly suitable for security engineers, network architects, penetration testers, and members of red and blue teams. Moreover, it&amp;rsquo;s an excellent choice for any security enthusiast who aims to test and enhance their understanding of network security.
In my view, professionals with experience in networking or cybersecurity will find the exam relatively easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TryHackme - Pre-Security Path - Review</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2021/07/tryhackme-pre-security-path-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2021/07/tryhackme-pre-security-path-review/</guid>
      <description>Ever dreamt of becoming a hacker or an IT professional? Or perhaps, you&amp;rsquo;re simply intrigued by technology. If you&amp;rsquo;re unsure where to begin, Try Hack Me is the perfect starting point for you!
Dive right into the new Pre Security Learning Path.
No prior IT experience? No problem! This learning path is designed to gently introduce you to the world of cyber security. Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse of what you&amp;rsquo;ll discover:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
