<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>warmup on Natan Maia Morette</title>
    <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/tags/warmup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in warmup on Natan Maia Morette</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nmmorette.github.io/tags/warmup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser Secure Command - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-secure-command-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-secure-command-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>Secure Command Introduction Secure Shell (SSH) is a protocol used to securely access and manage devices on a network. It encrypts data to protect confidentiality and integrity, making SSH a preferred option over Telnet for remote administration.
What is SSH? SSH is a cryptographic network protocol that facilitates secure communication over an unsecured network. Originally designed as a replacement for insecure protocols like Telnet, SSH ensures confidentiality and integrity of data exchanged between two networked devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser 007 - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-007-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/03/hackerviser-007-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>007 Introduction Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) has become an indispensable tool in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape, enabling seamless remote access to computers and servers from anywhere in the world.
What is Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP)? Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) is a proprietary protocol developed by Microsoft, designed to facilitate remote desktop connections between computers over a network connection. It allows users to access and control a remote computer as if they were physically present at the machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser Reddict - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-reddict-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-reddict-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>Reddict Introduction Redis, short for Remote Dictionary Server, has emerged as a cornerstone in modern software development, revolutionizing how data is stored, cached, and processed. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into the depths of Redis, exploring its features, use cases, and best practices. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned developer seeking to optimize performance or a newcomer intrigued by the buzz surrounding Redis, this blog post aims to provide you with a thorough understanding of its capabilities and potential applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser Arrow - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-arrow-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-arrow-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>Arrow Introduction Telnet, short for Telecommunication Network, is a protocol used for remote terminal connections, allowing users to interact with a computer or network device over a network. Despite its age and simplicity, Telnet still plays a role in various networking scenarios. However, its lack of security features makes it a risky choice in today&amp;rsquo;s cybersecurity landscape.
What is Telnet? Telnet operates on the Application Layer of the OSI model and uses a client-server architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackerviser File Hunter - Warmup Stage I</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-file-hunter-warmup-stage-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2024/02/hackerviser-file-hunter-warmup-stage-i/</guid>
      <description>File Hunter Introduction File Transfer Protocol (FTP) is a standard network protocol used for transferring files between a client and a server on a computer network. Since its inception in the early days of the internet, FTP has remained a popular choice for facilitating file transfers, despite the emergence of more secure alternatives. In this blog post, we will delve into the fundamentals of FTP, its operation, security considerations, and alternatives available in today&amp;rsquo;s technology landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
