<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cheatsheet on Natan Maia Morette</title>
    <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/tags/cheatsheet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cheatsheet on Natan Maia Morette</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Natan Morette</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nmmorette.github.io/tags/cheatsheet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>eJPTv2 - Cheat Sheet</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/ejptv2-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/ejptv2-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>eJPTv2 Cheat Sheet Disclaimer  This is merely a suggestion based on the tools I personally found useful during the test. I encourage you to take your own notes and tailor your preparation to best suit your needs for the exam
 For additional details about the Exam, please refer to my exam Review post:
Recommended Tools  Nmap Dirbuster nikto WPSCan CrackMapExec The Metasploit Framework SearchSploit Hydra  1. Assessment Methodologies  Ping Sweep fping -a -g 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Nmap Cheat Sheet for Quick Reference</title>
      <link>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/the-essential-nmap-cheat-sheet-for-quick-reference/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmmorette.github.io/posts/2023/12/the-essential-nmap-cheat-sheet-for-quick-reference/</guid>
      <description>The Essential Nmap Cheat Sheet for Quick Reference Introduction Nmap (Network Mapper) is an open-source tool for network exploration and security auditing. Widely used by network administrators, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for vulnerability scanning and network inventory. This cheat sheet provides a quick reference to the most commonly used Nmap commands and options, ideal for both beginners and experienced users.
Basic Scanning Techniques  Basic Network Scan: Command: nmap [target]  Use to quickly scan a target IP or domain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
